<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rakonto</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_reading">ReadingActivity</string>

    <string name="menu_account">Account Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="menu_accessibility">Accessibility Options</string>
    <string name="menu_help">FAQs</string>
    <string name="menu_author">Become An Author</string>

    <string name="help_0a">What is Rakonto?</string>
    <string name="help_0b">Rakonto is a discovery and reading platform for interactive fiction that supports language learning through bilingual multimedia interactive texts.</string>
    <string name="help_1a">How does Rakonto support language learning?</string>
    <string name="help_1b">All of our content has a base language and a target language, where the base language is the language you can read fluently and the target language is the language you are learning. Depending on the difficulty of the text, you\'ll be reading a mixture of the two languages that supports where you are at in your learning. You will get exposed to new vocabulary in context and have to make sure you understand what is going on in order to make decisions about what happens next in the story. You can save vocabulary for later to look it over, export it to your favorite flashcard app, or share it on social media.</string>
    <string name="help_2a">How can I use Rakonto in my classroom?</string>
    <string name="help_2b">Glad you asked! Rakonto\'s stories can be the perfect catalyst for getting students excited about language learning and exploring new cultures. Students can get practice reading, acquire new vocabulary in context, and challenge themselves to actually use their language knowledge to make decisions. You can create your own interactive fiction content or choose among existing content as part of your curriculum. With organizational accounts, you can monitor student progress and export vocabulary lists. Contact edu@rakonto.com to inquire about partnering with us, or visit rakonto.com/education for more information.</string>
    <string name="help_3a">Not seeing your question here? Email us at help@rakonto.com</string>

    <string name="accessibility">This is an early prototype of Rakonto, so we don\'t have accessibility features yet. However, we plan to let you adjust text size, switch contrast for reading, and other options so that readers with vision impairments (and hearing impairments for multimedia content) can still enjoy their favorite stories on Rakonto.</string>
    <string name="author">Contact publishing@rakonto.com if you are interested in writing for our platform.</string>
    <string name="account">This prototype doesn\'t have accounts, so there is nothing for you to do here. However, you\'d be able to log in/out, change child-safety settings, etc. Note that child safety can be modified either in account or preferences screens, although password will be required to turn off safety features.</string>
    <string name="preferences">This prototype isn\'t fancy enough to let you customize things, but here you would be able to change child safety, base language, language preferences (difficulty levels, favorite languages, etc.), automatic bookmarking, and otherwise customize your user experience.</string>

</resources>
